<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kyle Chang</title>
    <link>https://kwch3693.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kyle Chang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kwch3693.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://kwch3693.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kwch3693.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am junior at the University of Maryland College Park studying in Computer Science and Math . I am commited to learning and teaching. I was a TA for a 200 level computer science course. I plan on continuing to be a TA
What am I currently up to? Self Teaching:
 Real Analysis Number Theory Electric Circuits Design and manufacturing principles  Besides that I am working on my upcoming projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://kwch3693.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kwch3693.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Crime and Weather in New York Webpage Description This tutorial serves as both an analysis of relationship between crime and weather in New York and an introductory project for those aspiring to get into datascience. In our tutorial we dealt with problems like missing data and interpreting the data, all of which are invaluable in any datascience project. As a small spoiler we found that weather turned out to be a good predictor on crime frequency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://kwch3693.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kwch3693.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description> Epiviz Description Epiviz is primarily focused on providing a visualization of epigenetic data, with the goal of leading researchers/research groups to new discoveries and findings within the data. Check it out here
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>